<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/Jekylaarti/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/Jekylaarti/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-05T17:18:04+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Jekylaarti/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Owncloud Server Quickstart Guide</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Adding User</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Jekylaarti/jekyll/update/2019/04/04/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adding User" /><published>2019-04-04T11:46:21+05:30</published><updated>2019-04-04T11:46:21+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Jekylaarti/jekyll/update/2019/04/04/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Jekylaarti/jekyll/update/2019/04/04/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/images/Fig1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding user accounts
ownCloud is an enterprise file sharing service for online collaboration and storage. To access this service, the user needs to have their user account which is created and managed by the admin group.
Prerequisites for adding user accounts by admin team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Sign in to the ownCloud server 10.1 using an administrator account.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It will lead you to the user administration page, click on the username(admin).
A drop-down menu appears with options to enter the following sections: Personal, Users, Apps, Admin, Help, and Log out.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Click on the Users item from the drop-down menu. A default table appears displaying basic information about the users whose accounts have already been created.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;table&gt;
      &lt;thead&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.storywarren.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/space-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;space-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;/thead&gt;
      &lt;tbody&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Space&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;/tbody&gt;
    &lt;/table&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Create groups based on user’s access limitations.
To add groups, go to the Groups field. Hover over the + add group field, enter a name for the 	group and hit Enter. 
Now you can start adding users and adding them to specific groups as per defined access 	controls.
Adding or creating new user account
•	Enter the new user’s Login Name and the initial password
•	(Optional) Assign group membership 
•	Click the Create button&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: Login names may contain letters (a-z, A-Z), numbers (0-9), dashes (-), underscores (_), periods (.), and at signs (@).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ownCloud usernames cannot be changed. These are user’s permanent-owned cloud user IDs. However, user’s Full Name can be changed. The admin can also edit the passwords and can change user’s group assignments as and when needed. This is a useful mechanical mechanism for delegating some admin chores and enabling groups to manage themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After creating the user, you may fill in their Full Name if it is different than the login name or leave it for the user to complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: Press Ctrl-R to refresh the page. This is done to make sure your new entry is visible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To summarize, the steps involved in creating or adding a new user are entering a name and password and delegating the user to a group. The new user can now log in to the ownCloud server and start collaborating with other users.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>